Translated by MTX
Hi. My name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me.
but I have something to tell you.
that's gonna sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're gonna believe me
because you're very good
at telling when I'm lying.
E.V.. can you check the calibration
of my targeting matrix?
That doesn't feel zeroed in to me.
Checking target calibration.
Hey. E.V.. take five.
Standing by.
We used to know each other.
We were together.
But something bad was gonna happen
and the only way to stop it
was to make everyone forget me
First day at MIT. let's go!
Oh. my gosh! We're here! We made it!
MJ. come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest
you've ever been.
in your entire life right now.
I can't.
-Let's just do this! You're happy!
-Okay. okay. okay. Okay.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
I'm really. really understanding the culture
out here in Boston is just so different.
And sometimes
Spider-Man has to do the hard thing
even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart.
And everyone here is like.
"Pahk the cah by the hahba.
And maybe that's my responsibility.
To live alone with the truth.
But the truth is. MJ. that I love you.
And I hope that deep down.
something inside of you
remembers that you love me. too
Suspect is 5'8". 5'10". medium build.
But until then. I'm just gonna be Spider-Man.
Incoming!
Hey. get him!
Hey. hey. hey. Whoa. whoa. whoa!
Members of the Manfredi crime syndicate
were apprehended by Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey. we live on the same floor.
Cool.
Does anybody ever come up here?
Not unless they like asbestos.
We've just been using it for storage.
It's perfect.
Hey. everyone. sophomore-year-Ned is back.
Older. wiser. flyer.
ethegratefuln
Let's go!
-What is on your f face?
-How do you feel about it?
I mean. you look
like an assistant coach.
Huh
SO·79340
You sure you wanna do this. Scorpion?
Did you miss me. Spidey?
If I drop you from here
how long you think
it will take you to hit the ground?
Well. I don't know. You tell me.
Let's end this on a high note. huh?
Yo. Lonnie!
Wha ha happened?
DeWolff. all the evidence you're gonna need
is in the trunk of his car.
You tryin' to take my job. Spider-Man?
Hey. you-guys are the professionals
I'm just a volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
crime rates have dropped to a record low.
Police and Damage Control
give much of the credit.
to the masked hero.
Initiate HUD test.
Armed robbery at Civic Union Bank.
In the past six months.
he has taken down.
every major crime lord
across the five boroughs
including the superpowered
ninja group The Hand.
Near-Fat Oil Rig
Emergency
He is the pride of New York City.
The hero every grown-up relies on
and every kid wants to be.
Final semester. MIT.
Oh. my gosh. we're graduating in a month.
We've made so many memories.
Where do I begin?
Night swimming in the Charles River
with Jim and Wiley.
The infamous food fun at the Banana Lounge
Pulling all-nighters in Stud 5
with MJ and Nate Dawg.
It feels like yesterday
I was sitting on a roof with MJ.
dreaming about coming here together.
and I still can't believe we did it.
I'm so grateful
for all the friends that I've made.
I couldn't imagine
going through this with anyone else.
Ned. who do you think
is actually watching these?
I don't know. But maybe someone.
-Okay.
Okay. well. bye. someone.
-What? No!
-Bye. We're done. Yeah. we're done.
.
Promo Code:
for BONUS
for BONUS ibout
in proad day Promo Code:
for BONUS
Promo Code:
for BONUS gh pro
you know that swell was Promo Code:
High profile job like that.
you know that Foswell was involved.
Yeah. I hear you. but can you prove it?
Yeah. I'm going through
his financial records.
and I'm following his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know the saying.
"You do something you love
you don't work a day in your life.
-Mom. where's my calculator?
-I don't know.
Trust me. aight?
Being married to the job never ends well.
Well. don't worry about it. I'll be okay.
Oh. yeah?
You still getting them headaches. though?
Yeah. But I'll be fine.
I don't know. man.
I think you're body's tryin'
to tell you somethin'.
Like you need to get outta that suit
every once in a while.
Mom. do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know. Papi.
you need is some real human connection.
What? And we're not connecting?
Nah. dude. I don't know your name.
your face. or nothing about you.
don't think you've ever asked me a question
about my life.
Sure. I have.
Yeah. what are my kids' names?
Well. for starters. your son's name's Papi.
Is it Spider-Man?
I can't tell you that. sweetheart.
That means it's Spider-Man.
Gosh.
A hijacked tank is heading southbound
past 34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey. you getting this?
More work. Lucky you.
Okay. I'll see you out there.
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
POLICE
I got you. Spidey!
No. no. I don't need your...
Hey! Heads up!
You okay. kid? Yeah. you're okay.
See ya later.
You wouldn't know it just byjlooking at it.
but this very street was completely destroyed
in theBattle of New York.
ONLY $30!
Come on. come on. come on.
Come on.
Oh. God.
Hey.
The hell. Frank?
You just hit me with the van!
Quit your whimpering.
We're not doing that again. Frank.
You're goddamn right we're not.
This time you're gonna
get the hell outta my way.
You mean. instead of saving your life?
You gonna talk about
that Staten Island bullshit again?
Well. you said it. not me.
Jeez.
Look. man. you can't just shoot yourself
out of every situation.
Innocent people get hurt.
Who do you think's downrange of that tank.
dumb-dumb?
Suit yourself.
Jackass.
This freakin' guy.
Go home. Frank!
I'm gonna kill this kid.
-DeWolff?
-Are you gonna stop that thing or what?
It's heading straight
for the Damage Control Detention Center.
I'm trying.
Try harder.
There's a lot of scary dudes
locked up in there.
Well. who do you think put them in there?
Let's go. Scorpion. Moving day.
All right. everybody. clear out!
This guy is armed d and dangerous.
Get out of the vehicle. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spider-Man?
Where am I?
What?
Move! Move! Move!
Keep her for questioning.
Clear the building.
Enjoy the ride. Scorpion!
You won't be seeing much daylight
in supermax.
Scorpions are nocturnal. buddy.
The building is under attack.
Get the prisoner out of here now!
Sir!
You gotta take off now!
The building has been breached. Go!Go!
Hey. fire it up! Go! Go!
CONTROL
Change of plans!
Take him to the helipad at Bellevue.
-What?
-That's an order from Director Metzger. Go!
Now!
Copy that.
Hey! What...
How did I get up here?
Spider-Man. save me. would you?
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
Hey. Hey.
You pushed me out.
Interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
You know. the whole time
you've been chasing me
you forgot to ask yourself
a very important question
What's in the tank?
Go! Move
Spider-Man?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Hey. good job.
Hey. way to go. Spidey.
You guys okay? You good?
I swear. All the things they said I did.
I don't remember doing any of them.
It's okay. it's okay.
Look. let these people take good care of you.
I would never hurt you.
-Okay.
-I love you. Spider-Man
Yeah. All right. buddy. All right.
-Hey. what do you got?
-Here. get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue.
Ten minutes later.
a guard walked him right out the door.
What?
What about the tank?
Stolen from the Damage Control
warehouse in Brooklyn.
Driver was a janitor who worked there.
You got a motive?
Nada.
And no criminal record.
Scorpion must've gotten to her somehow.
Yeah. Maybe
What do you mean. "maybe"?
I mean. I don't know.
But I know someone that might.
Where you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm gonna go talk to someone.
Hi. is this 3250 Brighton Beach?
Okay.
I think I know what that means
Take off your clothes.
What?
You don't wear clothes in the banya.
Ditch the leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your text said that this was your office.
This is my office.
Get in.
I'm fine. thanks. I'll just..
My office. my rules.
This way you get to enjoy
a nice. relaxing soak.
and I get to see that
you don't have any weapons
and we both win.
Okay.
Really? What. you never take that off?
No. I... You know. it defeats
the whole anonymous thing.
Even for your girlfriend
or boyfriend or whatever?
There's a lot of conjecture online.
And super graphic artwork. Have you seen?
The one with you
and the ten Mysterios. it's.
I've seen it. I've..
It's hard to unsee. to be honest.
But. look. I don't have anyone.
I just kinda keep to myself.
All by yourself? All the time?
No wonder you're so sad.
-I'm not so sad.
-A little bit.
Could we just talk about
what I came here to talk to you about.
the attack on Damage Control?
Yes. So. that is more your area.
Like. small potato stuff.
Whereas the New Avengers
are focusing on big potato stuff.
Right. okay. Well. there's
more to it than that. you know
the driver and the others who were helping..
it was like someone
was talking to me through them.
Like someone was looking at me
through their eyes.
And you're wondering if it's mind control?
-Exactly.
-Like how they used on me in the Red Room
-And the other widows?
-Right.
-Right. No I don't think so.
I actually think it's probably
more like possession.
Possession?
Like a ghost or a demon.
-Oh. man.
-Or in Russia. we have leshy.
Leshy rules the forest and can possess.
Sorry.
Whatever it is.
they are looking for something.
This is the fourth attack
on the Damage Control facility this month.
And what do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today
there was a cross-agency cyber security aler
that got triggered.
Someone accessed
the Damage Control restricted servers.
using credentials from 30 employees
from the way station.
They all searched for the same thing.
V-Max.
Well. what does that mean?
I mean. it could be alien tech.
or secretive weapon programs.
or launch codes or..
I don't know. this is for you to figure out.
-This is small. baby potato stuff
-Okay. okay.
.not big potato brain stuff.
-You don't have to shout about it. Jeez.
Maybe I'll just go ask Damage Control myself
You know. you're not
completely anonymous anymore.
I've seen your belly button.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Oh. God.
Hi. I got an appointment with
Director Metzger. Yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human detected
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Heightened senses.
Exogenous DNA: Arachnid.
Please remove your face covering
for identity scan.
Oh. no. I can'tdo that.
-That's not possible.
-Failure to remove your face covering.
will result in defensive measures
Defensive measures? What are you talk
Guys. guys. guys!
can't take my mask off. I'm
Spider-Man.
He's all right. At ease.
My apologies
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger. Director of Damage Control.
How are you?
I'm good. thank you.
We had to beef up security around here
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
-No. not at all
-All right. come on This way.
This floor is mostly
research and administrative.
Downstairs. we have incident cleanup.
laboratories. agent training.
-Hey. what are they doing here?
-It's okay.
The Hand works for us now.
After you brought them in. I realized that.
fundamentally. they're a group of kids
without a leader.
All they needed d was a little direction.
Then. suddenly.
all the things that made them dangerous
turned them into an invaluable part
f our security team.
You can look at the many threats
that face us and see only danger.
Or you can see opportunity.
Okay.
Wow. look at that.
In the hands of Shocker.
these are a nuisance.
But it doesn't mean
we can't learn from the technology
or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to redirect destructive energy
into something useful.
That's the true meaning of Damage Control.
Be careful with that.
Right this way.
I wanted to talk to you
about the recent attacks on the agency.
There's been four. right?
Please have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with a threat
we can't control.
One we can't even see
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
also read Detective DeWolff's report.
believe you understand
exactly what t we're up against
Someone or something
that can hop into p people's minds.
But not yours.
No. I mean. it tried. but it couldn't.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if it were to get in here
and find whatever it is it's looking for...
the consequences could be unimaginable.
Well. let me guess. is whatever
it's looking for in that giant vault?
There are some things.
because of the nature eof my job...
I cannot tell you
But I believe you are our
best defense against this
You're the only one who can sense it.
re the only one who's immun
'm counting on you to defea
That's a pretty good speech. Director.
I'll do everything that I can. I promise.
Well. then consider yourself
a friend of Damage Control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
I wanted to ask.
the phrase V-Max"
doesn't mean anything to'you. does it?
No. Where'd you hear that?
It's just. you know
nature of being a superhero.
there are some things I just can't tell ya.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great. Keep it up.
I don't think Metzger knows
any more than we do
but I told him I'd do whatever I can to help.
You wanna help?
The best thing you could do.
is find Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah. I know. I have every camera in the city
running a facial recognition scan for him.
That sounds super illegal. Spider-Man.
I'mma pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah. probably for the best.
But look. if he shows his face. we'll know.
Do you have any mini-kegs?
Down at the end
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Easy.
Hey. also. you got any Sharkfire Energy?
Yeah.
Oh. no. no. no.
I don't want any. That stuff will kill you.
You know. all my friends
were drinking them during finals.
and now they're addicted.
I'm gonna need d you to not sell me any.
Memorize my face
lease do not sell this guy any Sharkfire
Sure. Whatever.
TAX
INSURANCE
Actually. I'll take one
Last one
Maybe two.
TAX 718-126-1919
Maybe two. ACCOUNTIN
TAX 18-126-1919
And then never sell me any.
TAX 718-126-1919 RENTALS
& ACCOUNTIN
Damn it.
Yo. Ned!
-What?
-Ned!
-Give me that.
-My guy. appreciate you
-Let's go!
-Yeah. man.
-Yeah! What time did y'all get here?
We came here. like. half an hour ago.
You need a drink.
Take this. take this. take it.
Thanks.
IRELAND
See you've stumbled across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos. I swear.
He actually saved me and my friends' lives
a few times in high school.
-Cool.
-Yeah. yeah.
And ever since. I've just been trying
to figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to the world or anything.
just to know. you know?
And to. hopefully. thank him face to face.
I actually created this app
that monitors his sightings.
Wait. you created Spidey Tracker?
You heard of it? Nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
Little chat room right there.
Now. we know he's definitely from Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow it down
to two prime suspects.
Science
Yeah. if you knew who they were
it would really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
Ned. by the way.
I'm
God there's. like.
50 people in our apartment.
Statistically speaking. that means
at least two of them are sociopaths
which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
They're a housewarming gift.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Okay. Most people just brought
beer and chips.
That's very nice.
I'm MJ.
I'm... I'm Maynard.
Maynard.
You two don't know each other?
VISIT HDHUB4U.AG
Nos'm-BHighbor.
Friend!bneigbber.
VISIT HDHUB4U.AG
So. howswas the jnterview?
I'm gonna thin water.
VISIT HDHUB4U.AG
It was nice to meet youpMaynard. Nerd.
you go? Please
you go? Please tell.me that yoy went.
you go? Please tell me that yoy went.
Yesh-HNAubWent.
And?
VISIT HDHUB4U.AG
Oh. my God that's amazing.
What?
Yeah. I don't wanna work
for some soulless corporation.
They're not all soulless.
Okay. They're all mostly soulless.
it don't you want. like. health insurance?
Yeah. of course I do. But at what cost?
Depends on your deductible
You mean. like. your principles?
-Yes.
-Sorry.
I don't know I know it sounds cheesy
but something is just telling me...
that I'ms supposed to be waiting
for something great. you know?
kay. Well. to waiting for something great.
To waiting for something great.
Well. the wait is over.
To your new home.
Dude. this is top-shelf.
Just like you.
I'm gonna hide this.
I lifted this off of him again.
But what if Ned needs
the fire of a thousand sharks?
You mean heart palpitations?
-You can't save everyone.
-I can try.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry. I gotta...
When we get into MIT.
we should live together.
-Yeah. for sure.
-Yeah. I'd love that.
Be a fresh start. And we'll all be together.
Yeah. no. you're right. Yeah.
Fresh start.
You're gonna forget who I am.
Forget who you are?
What are you talking about?
It's okay. I'm gonna come and find you.
and I'll explain everything.
-I love...
-Just wait.
Wait and tell me when you see me again.
My name is Peter Parker.
and I would like a coffee.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me now
that you've got powers?
You know. this whole thing
can get really scary.
You know that?
Well. yeah. it's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change.
like. very quickly
in ways that we can't even imagine right now.
Believe me. I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
Oh. God.
What?
I live here. I just.
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Is that my shirt?
No.
Cute dog.
Okay.
Hi. Peter. You have 107 new alerts.
Please check backlog.
What is happening?
HUMAN
HUMAN The results of your body scan
show a surge in the hormones
associated with your arachnid DNA
.resulting in the formation
of organic web spinnerettes.
and dangerously heightened sensory receptor
Okay. but I feel fine.
Prolonged isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing to this sudden change.
Have you experienced any
recent traumatic events?
Peter?
I'm fine. E.V..
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take some time to rebalance
Well. that's not really an option. is it?
Mechanical web shooters
and organic webs
cannot be used simultaneously.
Come on. Peter.
Alert. Senses are overloaded.
What the hell was that?
Your heightened senses
are taking in too much information at once.
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
All right. organic webs. Peter Two had 'em.
He was cool. You're cool.
Oh. my God. that's hideous.
Okay. here we go.
Okay. that didn't work.
Organic webs. Come on! And bam!
No. no!
Stop!
What's going on. E.V.?
Shots fired at the Damage Control Data Cente
in-Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Come on. Three. two
Web! Stop!
Web. stop!
Stop!
Web! Stop! Birds. birds. birds!
Web! Stop.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh. God!
Web! Stop. stop. stop.
I don't know what you're looking for.
I'm looking for V-Max.
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
Oh God oh. God!
PE8-692K
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
Scorpion. do we really gotta keep doing this?
My head is killing me.
You think I'm Scorpion?
What's happening to you?
ening to you?
You can't sense me anymore.
You.
What's going on with you. Spider-Man?
Warning. Arachnid hormones increasing.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
-We need some help over here.
-Yes. coming through.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
DeWolff. is she hurt?
Is she okay?
-Is she okay?
-No!
-Just let me go..
-Don't! What is going on with you?
That wasn't Scorpion. okay.
I mean it was. but he was possessed
by whatever hijacked that tank. okay.
-Look. please can I just...
-All right. listen. Slow down.
Listen. I don't know what this is.
but I need you to pull it together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
I know. I'm sorry.
If you act like this again.
I cannot protect you.
Whatever this is. you need to fix it.
Through lattice chromodynamics
we can arrange time and space in a grid
Which allows us to simulate
the quarks binding into the protons.
Cindy. is this a question about protons
or more stuff about Avengers?
Okay. Guys. I love to tell stories
but you know I gotta teach you
some physics at some point here.
All right. Let it rip. Cindy.
Well. if Thanos was so worried
about over-population.
why didn't he just use the magic glove
to make more food?
Arthur. you wanna a answer that question?
Hulk smash!
There you have it.
Excuse me. Dr. Banner.
-You okay?
-Yeah. sorry. it's just a headache.
Have you got a minute?
wanted to talk to you about your inhibitor.
Sure. Don't worry. It's got failsafes.
I'm not gonna turn into the big green
raging monster machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do see me
with this thing off run
No. but. you're using
target-specific short interfering RNA. right?
It's like gene silencing. you're just
incorporating the gamma radiation?
What'd you say your name was?
Ned..Leeds.
So you found a way
to suppress the expression of DNA
even as it's undergoing the mutation
due to gamma radiation. right?
-Yes.
-Okay. so. my question is.
would that same thing be possible
with DNA that's mutating for another reason?
ESU
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome
is mixed with some kind of foreign DNA.
Theoretically.
Theoretically? Yes. that's possible. Yes.
So. could you suppress
only some parts of that DNA expression?
Like the bad aspects
but just keep all of the good stuff?
You mean. like. if I wanted to keep
some parts of Hulk but not others?
Right.
It would be enormously dangerous
and complex. but.
if you were able to target
the correct mRNA strand
Possibly.
Wait. so you could just
turn the mutating gene on and off.
as long as you do it
before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean. if you apply the same thinking.
you could even.
develop some kind of automatic inhibitor.
that t would just adjust
to any type of mutation.
Well. now you're talking about
a universal inhibitor.
that would control anyone who has any powers
It's a dangerous idea.
Well. yeah. But it's theoretical. right?
You're not one of my students. are ya?
No. I'm a grad student.
I've...
I've taken enough of your time.
I gotta get some books back to the library.
The library is that way.
Right. Right. Duh.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Well. what parts of nature are good or bad?
What if you're trying
to control the expression
of something t that needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. Professor.
Like reptiles.
-Oh. God.
amphibians and arthropods
spiders shed skin
at key points in their life cycles.
The process is known as molting.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete.
While molting is a natural.
-part of a spider's life cycle.
-Okay. come on. Come on.
.it can leave the spider vulnerable
to threats.
Upload inhibitor beta build seven.
.process is initiated
by hormonal changes
Uploaded. Would you like to run a test?
Delmar's
Yeah runit
Yeah. run it.
WNLOADING FRAMEWARE
few hours to several days
NLOADING FRAMEWARE
Spiders have three stages
in their life cycle.
A LIFE IN WEBS: Journgy through the life cycle of a spider piders have three stages Autoplay
NistureTV 3 yoars
16.58 .. in their life cycle.
A LIFE IN WEBS: Journey thrpugh the life cycle. of a spider Autoplay
Each stage is characterized
by physical changes
A LIFE IN WEBS: Journey through the life cycle of a spider Autoplay
NatureTV 3 yoars ago
A LIFE IN WEBS: Jgurney through the life cycle of a spider th the largest changes occurring Autoplay
NatureTV 3 years ago
luring the beautiful transition to adulthood
A LIFE IN WEBS: Journey through the life cycle of a spider Autoplay
atureTV 3 yeare ago
For those who make it through
DELI
Dem DELI
molting amounts to a kind of rebirth.
DELI
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Delmar's Turning off video.
-Inhibitor active.
-Okay. here we go.
Come on. Come on.
Delmar's
Come on. Come on
DELI
DECI
Jrosh & Deli
Jresh & Delic
Keep an eye on my vitals
Inhibitor engaged.
Dolmar's
Suppressing arachnid hormones
to your baseline levels.
Okay.
All right. E.V.. let's do this
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert. Ink
Func
INHIBITOR OVERHEATING Alert. Ink
INHIBITOR OVERHEATING Alert. Inh
Func
Alert. Ink
INHIBITOR OVERHEATING Alert. Ink
Func
Alert. Ink
INHIBITOR OVERHEATING Alert. Ink
Func
Yeah. I'm sensing that.
Alert. Senses are overloaded.
Senses are overloaded. Alert.
Web grenades activated.
GRENADES ACTVATED
GRENADES ACTIVATED
Oh. sh.
Inhibitor field test one. failure.
Yo. Spider-Man. you okay?
Yeah. I'm just trying out some new tech.
Yeah. To get rid of that monster inside you?
Still can't sense me. huh?
Guess your technology isn't working.
You know. you're the only person
I've met that I can't.
hop into.
I'm sure that's really frustrating for you.
I'll get in there one day.
What do you want?
I wanna know why a half-human. halfspider
would decide to work for an organization..
whose sworn mission
is to hunt down anybody who's different.
Damage Control isn't after you
because you're different.
They're hunting you down
because you're dangerous.
Now. what do you want?
Since you're a very simple spider.
let me spell it out for you.
Damage Control has something that I need.
Oh. you mean V-Max?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it.
but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
You sure about that. Peter Parker?
You know. your apartment
is kinda like a parody
of where you think a sad single guy
in his 20s might live.
Take-out containers.
free weights. protein powder.
You're bluffing.
You know.
you're not hard to track down. Peter.
Well. at least not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing. though.
In of all places.
coffee cup.
RENTALS
E.V.. display home work station.
You spent four years
erasing Peter Parker from existence?
No wonder the spider's
trying to swallow up t the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you.
TUNE UPS
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
No. her roommate was nice enough
to post a new address online.
How about this? I'll race you there.
BKES-P
RENTAL
If you touch her.
Better start swinging
I'm fast.
Hey.
It's a long way to MJ's.
You better pick up the pace.
E.V.. track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical anomalies
between subjects.
Please stand by.
hank you all so much for coming today
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
in a race for the love of his life.
and it's not looking good
Come on. Spidey Keep up
Excuse me. Sorry.
Spider-Man!
E.V.. run these numbers with the others.
Analyzing jump distances for patterns.
Get me that jump data.
Calculating.
Come on. I need an answer!
Calculations complete.
You have a limit
to your jump radius. don't ya?
Thirty-three feet.
I don'ts see anybody up here
for you to hop into.
Very clever.
Like I said. you're not getting near her.
-Hey. hey. hey.
-MJ! I'm sorry. but you're in danger.
-Where's your roommate?
-What?
Where's Ned?
In Boston with friends. Why?
Okay. good. You gotta come with me.
What? I don't know
if you're the real Spider-Man.
-I'm not coming with you.
-We don't have time for this.
-Please. Come on.
-You need to get out of my apartment.
Look. this is gonna sound insane.
but there is someone who is after you
who is really dangerous. okay?
And I promised you
that I would keep you safe.
Please. you just have to trust me. Come on.
Fine.
Web. Stop.
Web stop.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Okay. We should be safe up here.
Okay. well. safe from what?
I'm not entirely sure.
Okay. well. what do they want with me?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would they choose me?
I wish I could tell you. I just.
We knew each other. didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me crazy for years
all the times that Spider-Man
saved either me or Ned.
It was the Washington Monument
and then it was London and Prague
and the Night Monkey.
I mean. twice is a coincidence.
but over and over again.
We knew each other. Tell me I'm wrong.
Well. you're wrong.
What were we?
Were we classmates or friends or something?
Look. I don't know what you're talking about.
Were we something more?
I just. I can't. I can't remember.
And I feel like someone scrambled my brain.
And you're the only one who would know why
This is crazy. I can't.
I know that you can't
tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of me
that still remerbers.
Peter.
MJ.
Hey. Peter.
I've missed you so much.
I can't believe you figured it out.
I did.
Go ahead. Peter. Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to for so long.
True love's kiss breaks the spell.
and reunites the star-crossed lovers.
MJ would vomit.
You really are a simple spider. aren't you?
I see why you like her.
She's..
she's smart.
funny
and a little dark and twisted
mean. it is sad.
There is. like. no thoughts of you in here
whatsoever.
But you knew that. didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you loved someone
the way that I love her.
then you'd know that
what you're doing right now is unforgivable.
Is that so?
You know. some people would kill
to hold the person they love one last time.
Stop it now.
You're running out of time. Peter.
Soon enough. it won't just be your friends
who don't remember Peter Parker.
Maybe you should write a letter to yourself
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now. Peter?
MJ.
MJ. No. no. no. Oh. God.
Oh. God. please. no. come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Oh. thank God. Oh. thank God.
Oh. you're okay. Oh. you're okay.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Stop. Wait. wait. stop. stop.
please. I'll quit.
You win. you win. you win.
Just don't hurt her.
You're a mess Spider-Man.
Anytime I want.
can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect MJ.
even from herself.
It really is a nice letter.
Little heavy-handed
But not bad.
You're okay.
I'm gonna take you someplace safe.
What?
Take me to 3165.
Lafayette Street
Navigating to Empire State University.
Wait. wait. wait! Okay.
-I got you. I got you.
-Are you sure?
-Yep.
-Okay.
'Cause I feel like
I'm slipping a little bit.
-You're not slipping.
-Okay.
You're okay. you're okay. you're okay.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Okay.
Can we just slow down
-for like two seconds. please?
-Well. we're almost there.
Yeah. yeah. but you just told me
I was mind controlled.
Well. not technically.
I mean. you're lucky
I believe in that stuff. okay?
Because governments have been doing it
for years. especially the French.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Look. Sorry. I'm just trying
to take you someplace safe. okay?
I don't feel safe.
Oh. shit.
-Sorry.
-Oh. watch out!
You're losing it. kid.
Thought you'd be able to see that coming
a mile away.
What is wrong with you?
-You could've killed us.
-Excuse me.
You show up to my house unannounced.
what do you think's gonna happen?
Wait. this is your house?
-No. no. Don't. don't. don't
-Who the hell is that?
Who the hell are you?
She's.
You know.
No. I don't know.
That's why I just asked you.
She's in danger. Frank.
Look. I need your help. okay?
-Yeah. looks like it.
-Well. come on. You owe me.
-For... Aren't you sick of this story?
-Staten Island!
Nah. Staten Island
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind. kid!
What. I gotta save it twice
-to get a favor out of you?
-That guy couldn't hit me.
-with a handful of rice.
-I mean. what does that sound like to you?
-I had him exactly where I want him
-A drug dealer was gonna shoot a guy
-I'm seein' him right there.
... then I webbed the gun.
.out of the drug dealer's hand
-I know exactly what I'm
.completely up for.
..and then kicked that drug dealer.
-Okay. fine. go ahead.
back into a storage container.
-What would you call that?
-What does that sound like to you?
I don't care. I just wanna go home.
That's an excellent idea. Kick rocks
-Go home.
-No. wait. wait. Frank. Frank. Frank. wait.
Please.
I have got to keep her safe. okay?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chill.
All right. Just..
watch out for the claymores.
Don't wanna pick up pieces of you
for the next two weeks.
Hey. I definitely would not eat that chili.
So. you telling me that maniac.
behind all that tank nonsense
is nothing but a goddamn teenager?
And it's not just the tank. it's every attack
on Damage Control this past month.
And how does a kid learn how to drive a tank'
I don't know. Frank.
-Beat you all over the street like that.
-She did not beat me.
This your family?
Would you get the hell away from that?
Look. I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
You don't move anything.
You sure as shit don't ask me
any goddamn questions about anything.
But she's classified as a telepath.
And now we have a name.
DCACG
"Jean Grey.
Yeah. These are the Damage Control sites
that she hasn't hit yet.
so if she surfaces.
then my facial tracking program
will pick her up.
Right.
Oh. yeah? What then?
Well. don't worry about "what then.
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it. huh?
I'm just supposed to sit here and
babysit your girlfriend?
-I don't need to be babysat. so yeah.
-She's not my girlfriend.
All right. all right.
Look. what's the plan. huh?
Just gonna hope that
your facial tracking program works?
And you get yourself killed.
I gotta watch her the rest of my life?
I'm not gonna get killed. Frank.
I can catch her. okay?
I just...
I just have to fix my inhibitor
and then I'll be good to go.
Well. what do you need to do that?
Frank. You do not have
what I need to do that. okay?
You know you've got some mouth on you.
What do you think.
you have an anti-static mat.
tonal probe. and micro tools?
got all that shit.
What for?
-Bombs.
-Bingo.
Unbelievable.
Hey. do you think it's safe
to maybe call someone
and let them know I'm okay?
Like your boyfriend?
No. Like my roommate
I don't think that's such a good idea.
you know. because
she already knows who he is.
and she can inhabit anyone she wants. so.
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. You're right.
-Sorry.
-No. it's fine. I totally get it.
If I called my boyfriend
he'd just ask me a bunch of questions
that I couldn't answer.
and then he'd tell me
I was being withholding again
-Withholding?
-Yep.
Sounds like your boyfriend's kind of a jerk.
But why'd he think you're withholding?
I don't know. You tell me.
masked vigilante behind the curtain.
Okay. I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well. do you have a Mrs. Spider-Man?
Do I have a Mrs. Spider-Man?
No. No
Why not?
Why not? Because I'm
I'm too withholding. obviously.
Welcome to the club
There was someone.
-Really?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
What happened?
I had to let her go.
keep her safe
I'm sorry.
That must have been really hard for you.
Yeah. it was. Yeah. It is.
t is really hard.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah yeah. I'm okay.
You know what. I'm just gonna come over.
Hold on. hold on. hold on.
What's going on?
It just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace
I was gonna major in biochemical engineering
so. do you mind if I.
Oh. yeah. for sure.
Here. There you go.
Wow.
So. does the device itself.
I mean. does it generate
any kind of radiation or a magnetic field?
'Cause that would definitely interfere.
Yeah. it has a micro magnetic field.
but I accounted for that in the design.
Okay. well. what about your suit?
It actually dissipates into the fabric.
which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles. or whatever you call 'em.
They would create a field.
It would be tiny. but.
But it's on your head.
which is very close to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
MJ. that is genius.
Okay. this has to work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay. That feels better
That feels totally better.
My head feels so clear.
Web. web.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
Oh. my God. MJ. that. like. totally worked.
You know. this is some really intense stuff
you're working on here.
Well. yeah. it's really important.
Yeah. but this is like. I mean.
this is like altering your DNA.
I mean. this is the kind of stuff you put on.
like. I don't know. like a monster.
Well. if you've seen what's been happening
to me over the last couple days...
then you might understand.
Yeah. well. I've been with you
for the last few hours
and that's not what I've seen.
And what have you seen?
From my side of the curtain?
A really good guy who might just be changing
Well. I don't mean to overstep.
I'll let you get back to it.
Can't sleep either. huh?
You want coffee?
Sure
You get your shit fixed?
Yeah. I've been wearing it all night.
So far. so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean.
it should completely shut down her powers.
You know what else would work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
Jesus Christ.
That has gotta be the goofiest shit
I ever seen in my life.
What. you can't even take the mask off
to drink a cup of coffee?
Don't take it personally. Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she. kid?
I don't know.
That's horseshit. Who is she?
-I'm telling you. I don't know who she is.
-What are you doin'? You care about her.
-You're pretending not to. Why?
-I don't care about her.
Look. I don't know who she is. Frank. Okay?
I don't have anybody. I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me?
What do you know about me. kid?
You think this is a choice?
Living like this. it's a lifestyle?
Is that what you think?
Kid. this is a sentence.
You know somethin'
If I had one second
people I love were still breathing.
you think I'd be hiding behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend
to be something that I'm not.
acting like a goddamn coward?
DOWNLOADED FROM HDHUB4U
OADED
She's at the Ramage-CentroLHQin Manhattar
DOWNLOADED FROM HDHUB4L
TRHUB4L
DOWNLOADED FROM HDHUB4U
gonna
DOWNLOADED FROM HDHUB4I
Thanks_
DOWNLO
DOWNLOADED FROM HDHUB4I
You just gonna let him go by himself?
You know I think he might need you
Kinda like you needed him on Staten Island.
Yeah.
CASEFILES\DAO1.
CASEFILEBYDADY CASEPELESIBADT
CABEFILESIBAO1 CABEYTLERADANY CASEPELEBIDADY
CABEFTLEUSDAOE CASEFILEBIDA
You can't hide from me forever. Bill.
You've got a strong door.
but it's the wall you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jean Grey
and you know what I want.
Jean?
You looked me up? I'm blushing
I told you what would happen to your girl
if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
And you're definitely
not getting inside that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Jean. you don't know
what you're dealing with
You know. you and Banner
have a lot in common
Both fighting a losing battle
against the monster that lives inside you.
Jean. this is the Hulk. you can't just
What the hell?
I see.
Trying to muzzle me like you muzzle yourself?
I can't let you in there.
Whatever V-Max is. you're not getting it.
Like hell I'm not.
Oh. crap.
Jean. don't do this.
Save your breath.
Frank. what are you doing here?
What you think I'm doing?
I'm saving you.
This is way above your pay grade. dude.
-We're fighting the Hulk.
-Oh. shit!
Really?
Get out!
-Stop shooting him!
-Are you out of your goddamn mind?
He's... Banner's not the problem! She is.
I thought I told you to stay home
and watch MJ.
Yeah. you did.
And then she tells me I gotta come watch you
Wait. did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing. daffodil?
I'm not blushing.
Goddamn it.
I knew I should have brought a bigger gun.
That's a good idea. "Bring a bigger gun.
What are you gonna do. tickle him to death?
No. Look. change of plan.
First we get this on the Hulk.
then we go after Jean.
I got one better
That's the highest casualty-producing threat.
You contain it. I go find the source.
I take it down. You got it?
Are you just trying
to get out of fighting the Hulk?
-I guess SO.
-Okay. whatever. dude.
I got this.
-Wait. no. Frank. Frank. Frank.
-What?
Do not kill her!
Don't start with that soft serve bullshit.
You know something?
I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do it my way.
Just... just go. just go.
And don't get within 33 feet!
So frustrating.
Hey.
This guy's got issues.
No. Oh. no.
No. not again. Oh. no.
Dr. Banner? Is that you?
Spider-Man. What happened?
Where am I?
-Hey. hey. hey.
-Did do all this?
-You..
-Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault. She was in your mind.
You weren't in control.
-I lost my inhibitor.
-Look here. here.
It's the only thing
keeping the monster inside.
It's okay. I got another one here.
I just need you to put this on.
-What is it?
-It's universal.
It should work on you.
Please. sir. there's people in the building.
Just put it on.
You okay?
My head. I think she broke something!
Is she still in there?
No
It's the other guy.
Bruce? Look. I can get you out of here. okay?
I just need you
to put that inhibitor on.
Get away from me!
He's coming.
I can't control.
Yes. you can. Bruce! Yes. you can!
Get out of the building!
Get everyone out of the...
No! No!
Banner. please. Look at me.
No Banner. No girl.
Only Hulk.
I didn't know you could get that big.
Good luck with that. Peter.
There you are.
Just hold still. Just hold still
Oh. God.
No lethal rounds.
Trackingt time to detonation.
Ninety seconds to detonation.
I know! I know!
Come on.
Why is your skin so thick?
Inhibitor cannot attach.
Come on!
Dr. Banner..
please.
Bruce.
It's Peter.
I'm your friend.
Bruce.
Throw down your guns.
or you'll get the next one in n the head
Where is she?
What did you.
It's over. Jean.
Sara.
Is that my gun?
Is anyone hurt? It's just me?
Is anyone hurt?
Spider-Man.
You saved my life.
And you saved God knows how many lives.
by making sure she didn't find
what she was looking for in there.
Still inside. We got her coming through.
Before she passed out.
she tried to say something.
A name. Sara.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her..
she managed to get in my mind for a moment
Sara was the name of someone
I worked closely with that recently passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of Sara
must have affected her.
Well. I'd love to talk to her
when she wakes up. if that's all right.
Of course. She'll be transferred
to our facility on Roosevelt Island.
Now. I'm just as eager
to get her talking as you are.
but let's not strain her too much in one day.
Yeah. of course.
Thank you. Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
MJ!
It worked. She's in custody.
You're safe now.
You left this.
Did you want me to find it?
No. No.
Look. I can explain. I.
Can you take that off. please?
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to have this conversation
with "Peter Parker."
You came to the party
at our apartment the other night.
And the donut shop.
The year I went off to school
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
Yeah. well. I've almost been killed. like
five times in the past 24 hours.
so it's not really working that well.
I know. I'm sorry.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Right.
So you just were gonna
make that decision for me.
I know. I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to keep saying
that you're sorry.
-I don't know what you want me to tell you.
-I want you to tell me
why you would do this to me.
I lost someone
And they'd still be here if it wasn't for me.
I didn't read you that letter because
I didn't want anything like that
to happen to you.
But that's not really
your decision to make.
I know it's not. but.
You mean everything to me.
And I've been trying to live my life
without you. but
I can't.
I love you.
This spell or whatever it is that you did
It worked.
All these memories that you're saying
that we have together. I don't
I don't have them
And I do see why. you know.
she would love you..
the girl you wrote that letter to. but
I understand
that you did what you had to do
to protect her.
And for that I'm so grateful.
But I.
don't love you.
Because I don't.
I don't even know you.
I should probably go now.
I really am sorry. Peter.
I don't have a phone.
Do you mind taking me home?
Yeah. of course.
Thank you.
LARPLU
-Thank you.
-Yeah. sure.
I'm going to
Yeah. yeah. Yeah. of course.
Do you wanna come up?
Just to say hi to Ned. Maybe.
I would love that.
Okay.
The Hulk. a.k.a. Dr. Bruce Banner.
is in custody
currently being transferred
to a psychiatric ward.
So sad
After years as a peaceful academic.
the question the world asked today is
"What finally snapped?"
Hey. I'm nearby.
-Hey. I'm nearby.
-MJ?
Yeah.
-Hey. I'm nearby.
Hey. I'm nearby.
You're not gonna believe this
-Hey. I'm nearby.
but the Spidey Tracker app.
.says that Spider-Man
-Hey. I'm nearby.
is in the direct vicinity.
-Oh. yeah? No way That's crazy.
-Hey. I'm nearby.
Hey. I'm nearby.
Ned. Spider-Man. Spider-Man. Ned
It's nice to meet you. Ned.
Hello.
-I'm not. like. a weirdo or anything. I'm.
-He's a little weird.
Why are you here?
-I was
-I was on a subway platform.
-She was in the. Platform. Right.
-And she was on her phone
-Yeah. and... Yeah. I got a little distracted.
-And the train was coming and he..
-I mean.
And I just swooped her right up.
-Yep. Saved me.
-Yeah.
Oh. my God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So what if you'remid-swing
and you decide you need to pee?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down to ground level
and run into a coffee shop a and you're like.
"Hey. it's Spider-Man. I need to pee"?
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No. I don't find a rooftop somewhere. Ned.
Is this really
what you wanna a be asking him right now?
Yeah. dude. come on.
you can ask me anything
You wanna know how my web shooters work'
I mean. I already know
how the web shooters work.
Is that right?
Well. there's obviously
some sort of a shear-thinning fluid.
that is cycling within a chamber. right?
So it can keep its liquid form.
And then. when you activate it
by pressing gon the triggers.
it runs through a Teflon turbine
and then it hardens
when it interacts with the air. Right?
I mean. not exactly. but.
Okay. okay. well. then tell me
what's in the web fluid.
I would guess something
like a long chain polymer
Nylon?
That's pretty close.
Okay. okay. What about Nomex or Kevlar?
"All right. then. Keep your secrets.
"If you're referring
to the incident with the dragon.
"I was barely involved."
"All I did was simply give your uncle
a little nudge out the door."
Solid reference.
Banh mi time.
You ordered banh mis?
I ordered five banh mis.
We have Spider-Man in the apartment.
He's gonna get fed.
Sorry about him. He's just. like.
very excited that you're here.
You kidding This is like.
the most fun I've had in years
I really missed you guys.
You guys really do look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
Yeah. I know.
When she was inhabiting you on the rooftop.
she kissed me.
and I kissed her back.
because thought it was you.
but didn't know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean. it's not like
I remember anything anyway. so
Really?
Yeah. It was weird. it was like.
one second I was sitting at my desk
and the next second
I was lying on the street.
I don't know. like a light switch went off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No. Why?
Metzger said he remembered
thinking about someone named Sara
but what you're saying
is that you don't remember anything at all?
I mean. yeah. it was instantaneous
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
heard you caught leshy.
Yeah. Her name's Jean Grey.
I need some help
determining the size of some potatoes.
-Potatoes?
-I think that's Black Widow.
I think Metzger lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a connection
between Jean and someone named Sara?
These potatoes sound meager.
Wow. That really is your office.
Well. well. well.
Internet. government records
and a lot of data related to Jean Grey
has been scrubbed by Damage Control
Data about what?
Her sister.
Wait. Jean has a sister?
Sara Grey.
Also a telepath.
Damage Control took her into custody
for study and observation.
Wow. I mean. you can probably guess
what they mean by that.
Experimentation
and other human rights violations.
Yes. exactly. Wait. who are you?
-Hi. Ned Leeds. Big fan.
-I'm.
Hi.
I'm sorry
I'm just so happy
that the sad man has friends.
Thanks. I owe you one.
Good luck. Spider-Man.
Bye.
She was just looking for her sister.
and I handed her to the people that took her.
-I gotta go.
-Hey. Peter.
Yeah?
Just be careful. all right?
Yeah. I will.
Spider-Man's name is Peter?
Jean. who do you want to be?
Her. Pink jacket.
She's too far.
You're gonna have to hop
Hop?
First. pick someone close.
And then.
Each hop has a limit.
But you can string them together
and go as far as you want.
And when you let go
You're right back where you started.
Could you do that
to everyone in this park at once
Well. yeah. maybe one day.
If you get really good.
How could she just.
send us away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that. anyway.
She was. before we changed.
Yeah. well. if that's all it takes
for you to stop being a mom.
then you're not a mom
What would you do
if you had daughters like us
I'd love them.
-Especially the redhead one
-Shut up.
We have each other.
And we have ice cream
-One mint chip. one chocolate?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Now I know how you're playing
59A38
-Get down!
-Get down! Get down!
Get down on the ground now!
-Down!
-Sara!
I'm sorry. Jean.
I have to keep you safe.
Subject is awake. Heart rate is 94 bpm.
Jean. that's not gonna work anymore.
thanks to Spider-Man.
Jean?
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay?
You're safe. Breathe
Where is she?
Like yours sister.
you've been blessed with a power
that has the potential
to do tremendous good in the world
or tremendous damage.
A power like yours in the hands of a child
is an impossible burden.
But imagine
if that powerwas placed
in the hands of people.
who actually know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're gonna change the world. Jean
Hey!
Frank.
I know where you are. what you're doing
Oh. yeah? And how's that?
I got eyes everywhere. kid.
ARCHIVE
SHARE
Look. Frank.
Damage Control kidnapped Jean's sister.
Jean was just trying to find her.
We were wrong about everything.
Sentimental horseshit.
You've seen what she can do
and what she's capable of.
What. you're gonna let her loose?
Is that what you're gonna do?
I'll tell you right now. you do that.
I handle it my way.
Frank. please. can you just.
Frank!
Distance check?
Forty-foot clearance.
Locking down the room.
Locking down.
Disengage inhibitor.
Jean. your powers are now fully operational.
WEBSITE - HDHUB4U.AG
As you_can tell.
we are bevond radius.
EBSITE
WEBSITE - HDHUB4U.AG
TellmsiwhatYu
You're the second person
WEBSITE - HDHUB4U.AG
I have weidea what that means.
She sent me3Hmassage
WEBSITE - HDHUB4U.AG
She wastrying tqbeUB mefind her.
She communicated with you telepathically
acrossall that-distance?
WEBSITE - HDHUB4U.AG
We did register a huge spike in that session.
Let's begin.
Our work with Sara centered on two areas.
identifying the source of her power
and identifying a path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record
a telepathic brain during a jump...
then perhaps we could I replicate
those pathways.
in a mind of our choosing
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together
over many months of trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what V-Max is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
RCANBING
TA
SCANNING
She's jumping.
Copy.
We're in full lockdown.
Process has commenced.
What process?
Hey. whoa.
that's a pretty serious look there. dude.
Hey. hey. whoa! What the hell. man?
Come on. I'm a friend of Damage Control.
What are you doin'?
It's gonna be like that. You wanna go
All right.
All right. well. just give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Do yous stretch? You a big stretcher?
I mean. you should do it
in your line of work.
What about you? You guys stretch?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
Watch your head!
Where is Jean Grey?
That's jump 26.
Recordings look good.
Excuse me. sir.
We have an intruder.
You were right.
She's much stronger than her sister.
Increase the frequency
You're doing very well. Jean.
SCANNING
Jean?
CANNING
SCANNING
Jean. can you hear me?
Jean?
You're a murderer.
Her frequencies are evolving.
SCANNING
This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my sister saw was this room.
Her brainwaves are esomehow
affecting gthe objects around her.
Shut it down.
I'm trying. sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister saw
was this goddamn room!
-Shut it down!
-I can't. sir.
Move.
can't let you do that. Bill.
The only hands that will wield this power.
are mine.
-What
-What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know. and I'm sorry about Sara
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong
If you came here
to save a helpless girl from Damage Control.
you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now
so do you.
Here we go.
God. that's cool.
Jean! Jean. please!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
What?
Isn't it funny.
how your friends from Damage Control
developed a special weapon
just for you?
They've got a whole task force ready.
Just in case you ever get out of line
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them
any more than they trust you.
I'm a little busy. Frank.
We got a problem. kid.
She got ahold of everyone
within a kilometer of the island.
Wait. what?
Hey. look. if you're gonna do something.
you better do it now.
I'm trying!
Kid?
Shit! Goddamn it.
My sister died.
in this room
surrounded by these men
And her only crime.
was that she was special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us
don't get to live a normal life.
We don't get to have friends or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over
So why don't you just
be honest with yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
I'm both.
Jean. please.
This won't make it right.
Come on. You're not a killer. Jean.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And know that losing her
felt like you'd lost everything
If you come any closer. he dies! They all do!
You know this won't bring her back.
right. Jean?
You.
Don't be so sure I can't get into your mind.
I'm a lot more powerful since I last tried
Go ahead
Hey
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me
now that you've got powers?
You know. this whole thing
can get really scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change. like. very quickly
in ways that we can't even imagine right now.
I know.
No.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always
make you feel really great about yourself.
but I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes you'll be really lonely.
And sometimes.
because you're special.
people can do dark. monstrous things to you.
But.
this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful
and the people who love you.
we love you not because you're special.
we love you because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when it feels like you're totally alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that.
no matter how powerful you become
Hey.
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah. you would've loved her.
Just because we've lost someone.
mean we have to do this alone
I mean. we can't.
Trust me. I've been trying
It doesn't work.
Even if that's true..
I have no one
You have me
Are you hurt?
No. I'm fine.
I'm okay.
-Peter.
-I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Peter. No.
Peter. Peter. No. no.
No. no. no. Peter. Peter.
Jean. you gotta get outta here.
They'll be looking for you.
No no. no. Please. just stay with me
Come on. hold on. Come on. please!
Jean. you're..
You're gonna be okay.
Just go.
Look at me.
Shock today. as Spider-Man arrived
at Bellevue Hospital with a bullet wound
seemingly at death's door.
PIDER
MAN
The reclusive crime fighter
is in critical condition
as the city's top medical experts
work to save him.
Tonight. all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved New York so many times
is now in the hands
of its best and brightest.
And the people of New York hold their breath
Frank?
Where am I?
-No. no. no. Hey.
-Where's my mask?
Don't worry about that. I got you covered
Hey. you're good.
Where's Jean? Is she okay?
Yeah. she's okay. She's okay
-Where is she?
-Kid.
think maybe she just left
She was using her magic voodoo shit
to keep youralive.
Yeah....she's all right
I'm sorry.
-Frank. Frank. it's okay.
-Just... I'm really sorry for what I did
-No. Frank. it's okay.
-And it's. no. it's a lot of things...
but it sure as shit ain't okay. all right?
I've seen..
I've seen real bravery. kid. in my day.
But that.
hat was something else
You crying. Frank?
No. I ain't.
You know. you look the exact way
I thought you would.
You know.
A nice kid.
Never had a friend like that
Are we friends now?
can't believe I just saw you cry.
I didn't cry. What are you talking about?
Bullshit.
Yeah. this.
They've been doing it all night.
They've been here since you walked in.
Just take a look.
kid. when you came in
they had to cut through the suit
but when you're ready to split.
I got a plan.
Dr. Moseley. 2495.
METRO
Hey. it's Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
Hey!
GENERAL METRO
THOSPITAL
METRO
THOSPITAL GENERAL
Yeah. Spider-Man!
THUSPITA
HAPITA
You're the best. Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
METRO
Over here! HOSPIAL
Over here! METRO
METRO
CLNER
We love you!
Spider-Man! Spider-Man! Spider-Man!
I've
Been thinking a lot about what you said
And you'd be happy to know
that I've decided I'm not.
I'm not gonna do this alone anymore.
I miss you. May.
mean. I've still got a little pain
in my back.
but I could probably get back out there
if you need me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know. I know. but come on.
you gotta give me something
I mean. how's the investigation going?
Well. Metzger's still missing. but.
your friend. Black Widow
she's been helping us dig through
all the records
Damage Control tried to have scrubbed
Had me drop by her office the other day.
And how was that?
Well. my skin feels amazing
Attention. all units.
We have a confirmed bank robbery in progress
Hey. are you getting this?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey. it's not that far from me.
I could probably meet you down there.
No. We can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You too.
Say hello to EJ and Marley for me.
Okay.
Spider-Man says hello.